<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Machine Learning on Antoine VILLATTE</title>
    <link>https://Anvil-Late.github.io/Portfolio/tags/machine-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Machine Learning on Antoine VILLATTE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://Anvil-Late.github.io/Portfolio/tags/machine-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 6 : Classifying Disasters on Social Media</title>
      <link>https://Anvil-Late.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anvil-Late.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-6/</guid>
      <description>This project is my take on the &amp;ldquo;Real or Not ? NLP with Disaster Tweets&amp;rdquo; Kaggle competition, in which we are provided a list of tweets that can either be about a disaster or not.
All of these tweets have been detected based on keywords such as &amp;ldquo;ablaze&amp;rdquo;, and it&amp;rsquo;s up to the competitor to build a model that determines wheter these words were used in the context of an actual event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 5 : House Price Prediction</title>
      <link>https://Anvil-Late.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anvil-Late.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-5/</guid>
      <description>In this project, my goal was to build a predictive model to answer the House Prices Kaggle Competition, in which we are provided with diverse data concerning houses such as quality, number of bathrooms, areas, in order to predict the final sale price.
The large majority of the work was spent on exploratory data analysis and feature engineering, with some data cleaning to do in both the training and test set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 3 : Weightlifting performance machine learning</title>
      <link>https://Anvil-Late.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Anvil-Late.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>A machine learning project in which I used fitbit-like sensor data from gyroscopes and accelerometers to predict the performance of a weightlifting exercise.
This project goes through the following key steps :
 Raw Data gathering and cleaning Model building - RandomForest Cross validation and Testing  Link to the GitHub repository</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>